<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<event category="CREATE" id="0">
  <actions>
    <action id="603" library="1">
      <!--action name: Code-->
      <kind>CODE</kind>
      <allowRelative>false</allowRelative>
      <question>false</question>
      <canApplyTo>true</canApplyTo>
      <actionType>CODE</actionType>
      <functionName/>
      <relative>false</relative>
      <not>false</not>
      <appliesTo>.self</appliesTo>
      <arguments>
        <argument kind="STRING">event_inherited()
image_xscale=2
image_yscale=2
myColor=make_color_rgb(40,40,40)

//Enemy base statistics
eName="Glitchy Pixels"
eLevel=35
maxLife=140
life=maxLife
pointWorth=52
atkPower=9
for(i=0;i&lt;6;i+=1)
{
  resType[i]=1
}
resType[4]=2
stunResist=2
baseItemChance=60
baseDropIndex=90
moneyWorth=5

runAcc=3
shotTime=30
shotDelay=80

orbitPos=0
orbitSpd=1
myDir=0
circlePlayer=0
bArmorBreak=0

jeremyText="Its movement can be a bit odd to interpret. All it does is orbit a set distance from your location, but that orbit is constantly changing, so your movement can make its movement look erratic. Stop for a moment and observe it, things will make sense then. As for attacks, it has one. When you see those small circles orbiting its main part start to move faster, it's going to fire three shots toward you."
chaoText="These are pretty weird. It looks like its sprite is undefined. You'll come across two kinds of these, both with the same behavior, but a different vulnerability. The one that has very contrasting color to non-solids when not in an inverted color is weak to PIERCE, and the one that has very little contrast to that is weak to SPECIAL. If you can hit it with EXPLOSIVE, but I don't know how useful that will be."
devText="I definitely wanted to use this idea again, especially after it was so well received in DT1. This time though, I wanted to take it a bit further with the color collision rules swapping and the method the traps use to conceal themselves. I thought this turned out pretty neat."

alarm[0]=1
</argument>
      </arguments>
    </action>
  </actions>
</event>
