<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<event category="CREATE" id="0">
  <actions>
    <action id="603" library="1">
      <!--action name: Code-->
      <kind>CODE</kind>
      <allowRelative>false</allowRelative>
      <question>false</question>
      <canApplyTo>true</canApplyTo>
      <actionType>CODE</actionType>
      <functionName/>
      <relative>false</relative>
      <not>false</not>
      <appliesTo>.self</appliesTo>
      <arguments>
        <argument kind="STRING">event_inherited()
makeActive()
setCollisionBounds(-21,-40,21,-1)
image_speed=0
image_xscale=-1
bCanTakeDamage=false

//Enemy base statistics
eName="Elpizo"
eLevel=20
maxLife=5600
life=maxLife
atkPower=7
resType[0]=2
resType[1]=2
stunResist=50
affiliation=9
bIsBoss=true
bNoBonus=true
dieEffect=0
bossProgress=0
activateBoss=0

//-- Movement Data --
moveSpd=9
chargeArc=3

//-- Neutral Data --
currentAction=0
lastAction=0
attackDelay=0
waitTime=45

//-- Dark Needle Data --
needleEnd=30
needleSpc=12
needleMod=5

//-- Bubble Data --
bubbleDecay=60

//-- Portal Data --
portalAction=0
portalDecay=180
portalArc=3

//-- Defense Data --
actNoTele=1
teleInc=0.75

//-- Special Data --
specProg=0
specTime=0
specMax=1800
specBackAlpha=0
specHP=15
specDir=0
maxSpeed=2
currHspd=0; currVspd=0
timeMod=0 //At 33% HP, if the Desperation attack has not been used at least once, the bar fills faster until the attack occurs

//-- Misc Data --
xCenter=448
yGround=416
roomSpan=320

nightmareZoneA=-1
nightmareZoneB=-1
nightmareZoneC=-1
nightmareZoneD=-1

deathAnim=0

jeremyText="This guy has a number of actions which all look to become harder as he's damaged. I recommend not jumping when it's not necessary if you're close to him. He has a move where he'll jump back and throw a super fast projectile toward you. If you don't have a dash ready when you're nearby, there's no chance of dodging it. There's also these nifty portal looking things that he'll use to shield himself."
chaoText="Elpizo is the antagonist of Mega Man Zero 2. Though in the end he wasn't really a villain. I guess I can see why the program read him in as hostile. That or the Virus is messing with things. At times, Elpizo will summon up those nightmare zones that slow down projectiles. If you touch those, it charges his super attack. Damaging his shielding portals does as well."
devText="The Nightmare Effect comes from Mega Man X6 and created random effects on the stages. The effect used in Gate D is simply that it slows down platforms and projectiles. Though it's an exclusive feature for this level, like the shadows for Gate C were, I didn't want the level to focus on it too much. The main focus is tight jumps and having the player make heavy use of the wall jump."
extraInfo="Capable of shielding and being annoying."

myHS=instance_create(x,y,oElpizoHitSpot)
</argument>
      </arguments>
    </action>
  </actions>
</event>
