<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<event category="CREATE" id="0">
  <actions>
    <action id="603" library="1">
      <!--action name: Code-->
      <kind>CODE</kind>
      <allowRelative>false</allowRelative>
      <question>false</question>
      <canApplyTo>true</canApplyTo>
      <actionType>CODE</actionType>
      <functionName/>
      <relative>false</relative>
      <not>false</not>
      <appliesTo>.self</appliesTo>
      <arguments>
        <argument kind="STRING">event_inherited()
makeActive()
setCollisionBounds(-16,-46,16,-1)
animSpd=0.2
image_speed=0

//Enemy base statistics
eName="Stalfos"
eLevel=10
maxLife=660
life=maxLife
pointWorth=26
atkPower=6
resType[0]=2
resType[1]=1
resType[3]=1
resType[5]=4
stunResist=12
affiliation=2
hitSound=global.snd_EnemyHitZelda
dieSound=3
dieEffect=4
bIsBoss=true
bNoBonus=true

initDir=0
runAcc=2
minDistToPlayer=88
bBroken=0
fixTime=0
xShake=0

atkTime=40
atkDelay=75

deathAnim=0

jeremyText="There's an iconic enemy. These guys are pretty stupid though. It'll try to keep itself at an optimal distance though and I wonder how much we'll see of that... Anyway, when you see his sword raised, he's about to do a dashing sword strike. If you're too close at the start of this, like the Wolfos, he'll dash back a tiny bit. Oh yeah, you should know how to finish them off after they fall; if you don't do it in time, they'll get back up."
chaoText="These guys are present in a lot of the Zelda games. I always liked the Stalfos from Ocarina of Time the most. In 2 on 1 fights, the one you weren't engaging with tended to not attack you. They were fallen Hyrule warriors if I remember right, and even though they were undead, I felt like they still wanted to fight with honor."
devText="Making this level with the upside down variants was tricky at times. There's a specific way I designed for the player to get through it, and every time I changed one thing to help dictate that route, it tended to make the level impossible. Making sure that by opening up another route didn't break this intended flow was challenging, but I found ways to make the level better through those iterations."
extraInfo="Vulnerable just before attacking."
</argument>
      </arguments>
    </action>
  </actions>
</event>
