<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<event category="OTHER" id="15">
  <actions>
    <action id="603" library="1">
      <!--action name: Code-->
      <kind>CODE</kind>
      <allowRelative>false</allowRelative>
      <question>false</question>
      <canApplyTo>true</canApplyTo>
      <actionType>CODE</actionType>
      <functionName/>
      <relative>false</relative>
      <not>false</not>
      <appliesTo>.self</appliesTo>
      <arguments>
        <argument kind="STRING">///SWAPPING FORM
if instance_exists(oWMC_IceHoverA)
{
  with oWMC_IceHoverA
  {
    bOrbit=0
    moveProg=2
    moveTime=fireDelay-5
  }
}

if superChangeAtk=0 //If Warmaster was about to attack, set back attack timer
{
  if waitTime&gt;=waitDelay-20 {waitTime=waitDelay-20}
}

bGravity=1; hoverMode=0
currHspd=0; currVspd=0

var tEffect;
tEffect=instance_create(x,y-(27*image_yscale),oEffect)
tEffect.sprite_index=sCWM_Ef_AtkPulse; tEffect.followID=-1; tEffect.newBlend=-1; tEffect.decay=-100; tEffect.xSpd=0; tEffect.ySpd=0
tEffect.image_xscale=1.25; tEffect.image_yscale=1.25
shiftTime=0; shiftDamage=0
if ATTACK_FORM=1
{
  sprite_index=sWarmasterA_Idle
  jeremyText="The Warmaster is able to employ a wide range of close range sword attacks. Which is trouble for you because he's practically immune to most of your projectiles. He's got a standard sword attack that also launches a fairly close range wave. A dash, jump, and dive attack. Jerry, you cover a lot of space with your sword, but Claire, you have good range. Keep that in mind. He can cling to the walls too and when you see that, he's got quite a nasty energy attack from the ceiling that he can summon."
  chaoText="I figured there was a lot more he could do. When I first saw the Warmaster, I was wondering if he'd be able to employ those Mega Man ZX abilities like this."
  for(i=0;i&lt;6;i+=1)
  {
    resType[i]=3
  }
  resType[1]=2; resType[2]=1; resType[3]=1; resType[4]=2; resType[5]=1
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=2 {resType[1]=1}
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=3 {resType[4]=1}
  if shiftType=0 {shiftDmgMax=42; shiftMaxTime=750}
  else {shiftDmgMax=30; shiftMaxTime=660}
}
else if ATTACK_FORM=2
{
  sprite_index=sWarmasterB_Idle
  jeremyText="Oh wow, so he CAN do a lot more. Okay, something worth noting is that all of his fire attacks are counted as Explosive damage. The biggest threat with this form that I can see is his charge attack. It's super fast and leave a bunch of fire pillars along his path. I doubt you'll be able to reliably use i-frames to avoid damage, so keep their spacing in mind. That and I think it would be best if you didn't dash when unnecessary."
  chaoText="Uh oh, things suddenly got a lot worse for you guys. It looks like he can do the same type of thing you two can do. He'll periodically swap forms to match the situation. I'm sure he's got a limitation on when he can swap... at least I hope so. Would suck if he started combining attacks from the different forms..."
  for(i=0;i&lt;6;i+=1)
  {
    resType[i]=3
  }
  resType[0]=2; resType[3]=1; resType[4]=1; resType[5]=2
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=2 {resType[0]=1}
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=3 {resType[1]=1; resType[5]=1}
  if shiftType=0 {shiftDmgMax=81; shiftMaxTime=750}
  else {shiftDmgMax=60; shiftMaxTime=660}
}
else if ATTACK_FORM=3
{
  bGoombaStomp=1; goombaStompTime=15
  numOfAtks=0
  sprite_index=sWarmasterC_Idle
  jeremyText="In this form, he can hover and he'll do it very often. I'd recommend Claire stay active for this one since she's got a bit more maneuverability and she has the Morph Ball for tight bullet storms. He can spam projectiles in this form quite a bit and he's rather scary with those projectile patterns as well. Just a thought I had. Learn his attacks and his openings. If he starts going crazy with attacks, keep calm and wait for moments to counter."
  chaoText="If you haven't noticed yet, he telegraphs EVERY attack before he performs them, though he does get faster the more you damage him. There's something else I've noticed. He has a sort of 'super attack' per form, but each of those can only be used after he charges up enough. It looks like all he has to do to charge is use his wide variety of standard attacks."
  for(i=0;i&lt;6;i+=1)
  {
    resType[i]=3
  }
  resType[0]=1; resType[1]=1; resType[2]=1; resType[5]=2
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=2 {resType[5]=1}
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=3 {resType[4]=1}
  if shiftType=0 {shiftDmgMax=132; shiftMaxTime=750}
  else {shiftDmgMax=90; shiftMaxTime=660}
}
else if ATTACK_FORM=4
{
  sprite_index=sWarmasterD_Idle
  jeremyText="I'd recommend staying away from this form mainly due to his ability to call up tornados around him. He's immune to melee damage in this form anyway. While he doesn't spam projectiles too bad in this form, the projectiles he does have are large. He has a lot of field control in this form, though I don't feel it's as significant as his main one, luckily for you."
  chaoText="He's fast in this form and tends to use his own body as his weapon along with his wind attacks and blade strikes. That seeking wind orb that he summons isn't so bad until he starts covering the field in tornados. If he's close to the middle of the field, you have to dash to dodge those. Keep that in mind when managing your dash energy."
  for(i=0;i&lt;6;i+=1)
  {
    resType[i]=3
  }
  resType[0]=1; resType[1]=1; resType[2]=2; resType[4]=2
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=2 {resType[3]=1}
  if DIFFICULTY&gt;=3 {resType[2]=1; resType[4]=1}
  if shiftType=0 {shiftDmgMax=75; shiftMaxTime=750}
  else {shiftDmgMax=54; shiftMaxTime=660}
}
</argument>
      </arguments>
    </action>
  </actions>
</event>
